The competing valley network is considered to be behind and now prosecution for the murder trial \ h on the east in town in Umeå has arrived and the trial is ongoing in November.
The prosecutors raise a case of a case where eight people are charged with a person in a \ hom, among other things.
Murder attempts, serious drug crimes and extremely serious weapons offenses.
Police have pointed out a 23-year-old man as the brain behind the shooting.
He is suspected of instigating attempts at murder, serious drug crime and serious weapons crime.
The event is considered to be part of the incredibly intense and bloody conflict between the Foxtrot and the Dalen Network.
This \ here a settlement in criminal circles.
These are organized activities where you want to control the drug market in Umeå and Skellefteå.
According to the indictment, the business has been ruled by the 23-year-old who has stayed in Spain and the Netherlands before being arrested in The Hague in the Netherlands.
He is suspected of having a person to Umeå to ensure that the shooting is carried out properly.
Of the eight \ Håtalade, seven are detained and one person is on the loose.
The 23-year-old who is said to be behind the shooting in Umeå is described by the police as a driving force in a constellation who conducted drug trafficking in the city.
When he was arrested at a tavern in late 2022, he threatened both police and guards by force.
- Health "Police Chief's \ Hame" that it is war now!
He screamed among other things.
The 23-year-old man \ here linked to the violent dalen network.
The man was indicted in \ HJANUSURE for abuse, attempted violence against an official, violent resistance, drug crime and illegal threats.
But the trial never took place.
According to documents from the Prison and Probation, the man had gone abroad and stayed away.
The police conduct a number of house searches after the arrest and on April 18 a larger amount of drugs and most weapons are found on Bryggargatan and on Tegsplan in Umeå.
In connection with the investigation work linked to this case, a large number of phones are taken into account and in the analysis work of these phones, the police have identified a signal alias called "Don Svensson" which has a significant role linked to the investigation.
In connection with investigative measures regarding the attempted murder, the drug and the weapons, it has subsequently cleared up a picture that the cases regarding the murder attempt, Bryggargatan and Tegsplan are closely linked to each other.
Information has also emerged during the investigation that several people in Oliver and Liam's circle have been involved in the acts in various ways.
Through the investigative measures, a picture has also been crystallized that John, the 23-year-old, has held a leading and governing position in handling from abroad.
The victim described the incident as a person shot him with a gun.
The first shot must have hit the stomach and the victim must then have fallen over.
Then two or three shots came into rapid succession and he must then have run (against the witnesses) for help.
The victim survived the attempted murder but in September 2023 he was arrested by the police's force.
He was linked to a drug heritage linked to a large seizure at a workplace in Umeå worth SEK 600,000 in March 2023.
Large sums of cash were also found in his apartment.
The victim, Patrik, is sentenced to two years in prison by Umeå District Court for serious drug crime.
In interrogation with the accused Sagittarius, who admits that he fired the shots, he described that from a jacket pocket he produced a gun from a few meters to perhaps two meters away, three shots fired at the victim.
Amphetamine, 3-CMC, MDMA, cannabis resin, oxycodone, pregabalin, alprazolam etc
Them defendants are:
Liam, 20, the recognized shooter is charged with attempted murder, serious weapons crime, extremely serious weapons crime, serious drug crime and violation of the Flammable and Explosive Goods Act.
Oliver aka "shiesty", 21 years, is charged with attempted murder, extremely serious weapons crime, serious drug crime, violation of the Flammable and Explosive Goods Act.
Liam and Oliver have together tried to kill Patrik by Liam armed with a semi -automatic gun and repeatedly shot Patrik to the body.
Oliver has been involved in the specified deed by planning and organizing the shooting together with Liam during the period in April until the attempted murder.
They have been in contact with John, who ordered the deed, Oliver has conveyed the assignment to Liam.
Oliver and Liam have subsequently reported to John that they completed the assignment by contacting him after the shooting took place.
John Aka Don Svensson, 23, is charged with extremely serious weapons crime and the instigation of attempted murder.
John has managed to try to kill Patrik by preferably through extensive contacts with Liam and Oliver through encrypted telephone traffic
Provide instructions to them to shoot Patrik and by ensuring that a person monitored the execution of the shooting.
Do you think the men will be folded and what will this have for Umeå in the future?